Sam, you realize feeding that bear is illegal?
Well, good thing he's not a bear. He's family.
Good day, ma'am.
Good morning to you, Benny.
You know the drill. We're going to need backup.
Copy that, sending units.
Morning, ma'am. We see you finally stop with that bear.
All right, have a good one.
There you go, big fella. Nice and easy.
Got an apple for you today. Good boy.
Cold out, isn't it?
Look at you go, Benny.
Higher than me that time. Careful, ma'am.
Ma'am, you can't keep feeding that bear.
It's not safe for you or the neighbors.
This isn't a bear officer. He's family.
He's been coming around for almost 10 winners now.
Family are not. He's still a wild animal.
Look.
Benny.
Good boy, Benny.
Oh, I didn't see you there.
Let me guess. You're going to want some of this dinner, huh, big fella?
You sure are spoiled, Benny.
Ma'am, what did we tell you about feeding that bear?
I don't have no bowl in my hand today.
Now do all of sir.
Good day, ma'am.
Ma'am, you really can't be running a petting zoo out here.